<resources>
    <!-- Title -->
    <string name="app_name">Werewolf</string>
    <string name="title_menu">Werewolves of Miller\'s Hollow</string>

    <!-- Characters -->
    <string name="Actor">Actor</string>
    <string name="Angel">Angel</string>
    <string name="BearTamer">Bear Tamer</string>
    <string name="BigBadWolf">Big Bad Wolf</string>
    <string name="Brother">Brother</string>
    <string name="Crow">Crow</string>
    <string name="Cupid">Cupid</string>
    <string name="Defender">Defender</string>
    <string name="Elder">Elder</string>
    <string name="Fireman">Arsonist</string>
    <string name="Fox">Fox</string>
    <string name="Gypsy">Gypsy</string>
    <string name="Hunter">Hunter</string>
    <string name="Idiot">Idiot of the Village</string>
    <string name="LittleGirl">Little Girl</string>
    <string name="Manipulator">Manipulator</string>
    <string name="Piper">Flute Player</string>
    <string name="RustyKnight">Rusty Knight</string>
    <string name="Scapegoat">Scapegoat</string>
    <string name="Seer">Seer</string>
    <string name="Servant">Devoted Servant</string>
    <string name="Sister">Sister</string>
    <string name="StutteringJudge">Stuttering Judge</string>
    <string name="Thief">Thief</string>
    <string name="Villager">Villager</string>
    <string name="VillagerVillager">Villager-Villager</string>
    <string name="Werewolf">Werewolf</string>
    <string name="WhiteWerewolf">White Werewolf</string>
    <string name="WildChild">Wild Child</string>
    <string name="Witch">Witch</string>
    <string name="WolfFather">Wolf Father</string>
    <string name="WolfHound">Wolf Hound</string>
    <string name="Phase_SLEEPING">Sleeping</string>
    <string name="Phase_NIGHT">Night</string>
    <string name="Phase_DAWN">Dawn</string>
    <string name="Phase_DAY">Day</string>
    <string name="Phase_SUNSET">Sunset</string>
    <string name="Power_PERMANENT">Permanent</string>
    <string name="Power_CONSUMABLE">Consumable</string>
    <string name="Power_CONDITIONAL">Conditional</string>
    <string name="Power_UNIQUE">Unique</string>
    <string name="Condition_NOCONDITION">No condition</string>
    <string name="Condition_ONEWEREWOLF">One Werewolf</string>
    <string name="Condition_ONEVILLAGER">One Villager</string>
    <string name="Condition_ALLWEREWOLVES">All Werewolves</string>
    <string name="Condition_ALLVILLAGERS">All Villagers</string>
    <string name="Condition_LINKEDROLES">Linked Roles</string>
    <string name="Condition_ISALONE">Is solitary</string>

    <!-- Generic -->
    <string name="Generic_Yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="Generic_No">No</string>
    <string name="Generic_Cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="Generic_Back">Back</string>
    <string name="Generic_Okay">OK</string>
    <string name="Generic_NotFoundedString">String not found!</string>

    <!-- Menu buttons -->
    <string name="MenuButton_StartGame">Start</string>
    <string name="MenuButton_Role">Roles</string>
    <string name="MenuButton_FAQ">F.A.Q.</string>
    <string name="MenuButton_Exit">Exit</string>

    <!-- Select buttons -->
    <string name="SelectButton_StartGame">Begin</string>
    <string name="SelectButton_Previous">&lt;</string>
    <string name="SelectButton_Next">&gt;</string>
    <string name="SelectButton_Cancel">C</string>
    <string name="SelectButton_Delete">X</string>

    <!-- Game buttons -->
    <string name="GameButton_Roles">Roles</string>
    <string name="GameButton_NextTurn">Next turn</string>
    <string name="GameButton_Information">Info</string>
    <string name="GameButton_EndGame">End the game</string>

    <!-- Main View -->
    <string name="MainView_Language">Language</string>

    <!-- Role View -->
    <string name="RoleView_DialogTitle">Elder power</string>
    <string name="RoleView_DialogDescription">Do you wish to remove the powers of all the villagers not solo?</string>
    <string name="RoleView_AncientButton">Elder</string>

    <!-- Information View -->
    <string name="InformationView_title">Description</string>
    <string name="InformationView_death">Deaths</string>
    <string name="InformationView_deathEdit">Enter the deaths</string>
    <string name="InformationView_lover">Lovers</string>
    <string name="InformationView_loverEdit">Enter the lovers</string>
    <string name="InformationView_defender">Defender</string>
    <string name="InformationView_defenderEdit">Enter the protected</string>
    <string name="InformationView_wildChild">Wild Child</string>
    <string name="InformationView_wildChildEdit">Enter the mentor</string>
    <string name="InformationView_bearTamer">Bear</string>
    <string name="InformationView_bearTamerEdit">Enter the tamer</string>
    <string name="InformationView_ancient">Ancient</string>
    <string name="InformationView_ancientEdit">Enter the ancient</string>
    <string name="InformationView_infected">Infected</string>
    <string name="InformationView_infectedEdit">Enter the infected</string>
    <string name="InformationView_sectarian">Sectarian</string>
    <string name="InformationView_sectarianEdit">Enter the designated players</string>
    <string name="InformationView_comedian">Comedian</string>
    <string name="InformationView_comedianEdit">Enter the copied role</string>
    <string name="InformationView_thief">Thief</string>
    <string name="InformationView_thiefEdit">Enter the trapped player</string>
    <string name="InformationView_piper">Piper</string>
    <string name="InformationView_piperEdit">Enter the bewitched</string>
    <string name="InformationView_scapegoat">Scapegoat</string>
    <string name="InformationView_scapegoatEdit">Enter the allowed voters</string>
    <string name="InformationView_switched">Seat changes</string>
    <string name="InformationView_switchedEdit">Enter the players who switched seats</string>
    <string name="InformationView_punished">Punished</string>
    <string name="InformationView_punishedEdit">Enter the punished</string>

    <!-- Select View -->
    <string name="SelectView_NumberOfCharacters">Number of characters selected : %1$d</string>
    <string name="SelectView_selectionTitle">Select an item</string>
    <string name="SelectView_selectionMessage">Selected version of %s : %s</string>
    <string name="SelectView_clearButton">Clear</string>
    <string name="SelectView_clearDialogTitle">Clear the list</string>
    <string name="SelectView_clearDialogMessage">You\'re about to clear the list of selected characters for your game. Are you sure you want to do this ?</string>

    <!-- Game View -->
    <string name="GameView_StartGame">Start the game</string>
    <string name="GameView_BadInit">No game</string>
    <string name="GameView_GameOver">Game over</string>
    <string name="GameView_Header">Phase %1$s, turn %2$d</string>
    <string name="GameView_phaseSleeping">The night has come, the village goes to sleep!</string>
    <string name="GameView_phaseDawn">Morning, proceed with the eliminations!</string>
    <string name="GameView_phaseDay">Day time! Chat and speak about what to do!</string>
    <string name="GameView_phaseEvening">Dinner is served! But watch out, these villagers are alive, so are their enemies…</string>
    <string name="GameView_numberCharacters">Number of characters in game : %1$d</string>

    <!-- Description View -->
    <string name="DescriptionView_CreationButton">Create</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_EditionButton">Edit</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_DeletionButton">Delete</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_ResetButton">Reset</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionSoloYes">Solitary : Yes,</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionSoloNo">Solitary : No,</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionWakeUpYes">Wakes up at night : Yes,</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionWakeUpNo">Wakes up at night : No,</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionPower">Power : %s</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_statDescriptionCondition">Condition : %s</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_DeleteQuestion">Do you wish to delete this role?</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_ResetQuestion">Do you wish to reset all the roles and delete the ones you created?</string>
    <string name="DescriptionView_DialogTitle">Description</string>

    <!-- Creation View -->
    <string name="CreationView_Picture">Picture</string>
    <string name="CreationView_SoloSpinner">Solitary</string>
    <string name="CreationView_SoloText">Determines if the role is solitary. Solitary roles do not belong to any team, and must fulfill their own objectives to win by themselves. Roles that are not solitary can influence the behavior of the app, like the Ancient which removes the powers of all special villagers on death.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_NocturneSpinner">Nocturnal</string>
    <string name="CreationView_NocturneText">Determines if the role wakes up at night.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_WerewolfSpinner">Werewolf</string>
    <string name="CreationView_WerewolfText">Determines if the role is considered as a Werewolf.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_Mode">Mode</string>
    <string name="CreationView_HintMode">Enter your title mode</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ModeText">Enter the role\'s identifier key. The \"NORMAL\" and \"AUTHOR\" keys are reserved and cannot be used.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_PowerSpinner">Power</string>
    <string name="CreationView_PowerText">Specifies the category of the power used by the role : \nPERMANENT : The power is always active. Use this option when the role has no power.\nCONSUMABLE : The power can be consumed at any time during the game. You will be able to change the \"Wakes up at night\" option in the roles view to deactivate the role. If the role is supposed to wake up at night in later turns, change the configuration setting accordingly.\nCONDITIONAL : The power can be activated based on a condition set up in the following dropdowns.\nUNIQUE : The power is usable one time, the role will not be woken up at night afterwards. Usable only on roles that wake up at night.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ConditionSpinner">Condition</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ConditionText">You must choose the \"CONDITIONAL\" power to edit this parameter. Specifies the role\'s wake up conditions : \nNOCONDITION : The default value, used for powers that are always active. \nONEWEREWOLF : The player wakes up when at least one Werewolf is dead. \nONEVILLAGER : The player wakes up when at least one simple Villager is dead. \nALLWEREWOLVES : The player wakes up when all Werewolves are dead. \nALLVILLAGERS : The player wakes up when all simple Villagers are dead. \nLINKEDROLES : The player wakes up when all the specified roles are dead. \nISALONE : The player wakes up when they\'re the last one in play with this role. Works only with roles that can have multiple occurrences.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_Linked">Linked roles</string>
    <string name="CreationView_LinkedText">Select the roles to link. Each link is named based on a combination of the target role\'s name and version. The player will wake up at the same time as the roles it has been linked with. If you need to create a new Werewolf that has a second turn, use the \"Werewolf\" option instead.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_LinkedButton">Link</string>
    <string name="CreationView_Action">Action</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ActionHint">Night action</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ActionText">Specify the text that will appear when the role is woken up at night. This text is never shown if the role does not wake up at night.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_Description">Description</string>
    <string name="CreationView_DescriptionHint">Description of your role</string>
    <string name="CreationView_DescriptionText">Specify the actions performed by the role.</string>
    <string name="CreationView_ValidButton">Create</string>
    <string name="CreationView_Title">Role Creation</string>

    <!-- FAQ View -->
    <string name="FaqView_title">F.A.Q.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_null">No content available.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question1">In one sentence, what is this app about?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer1">This app is a helper for your Werewolves of Miller\'s Hollow games.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question2">How does it work?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer2">Start a game, add the characters in play, and you are set!</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question3">Why can I start a game with no Werewolves in play?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer3">This allows you to play the \"Black Death\" variant of the game where there are no Werewolves in play. Read the manual for more information on the \"Black Death\" variant.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question4">What the heck? Why aren\'t players woken up in the order specified by the manual?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer4">The app allows you to customize the turn order. If you want to start with the Werewolves, you can! Use the buttons at the bottom of the role selection screen to reorder them.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question5">Special note for the turn order:</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer5">Simple roles linked to the Werewolves will follow them when they are reordered. This is also applied to the Little Girl in normal mode, which wakes up at the same time as the Werewolves.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question6">Why does this not apply to the White Wolf and the Big Bad Wolf?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer6">They are not linked to the Werewolves so they can play their special turn. Note that the app will call the White Wolf every night instead of every two nights as originally intended.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question7">What is the version of a role?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer7">Werewolves of Miller\'s Hollow is not a fair and balanced game, and also has some roles that aren\'t fun to everyone. To fix this, most of them have a special version I, the developer, created and tested in game with good feedback!</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question8">How to play the base Thief role?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer8">The base Thief role does not have its use in the app since the player takes one of two roles that are not in play, at the beginning of the game. For this specific case, I advise to add both roles in the turn order, and deactivate the Thief and the role they have not chosen once they have been woken up on the first night.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question9">Your Thief is strange… what is this version with traps?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer9">My Thief with traps is inspired from fantasy worlds where thieves master this skill. Try it, you can be surprised how fun it can be for the players! Make sure to keep track of the kind of trap that was used and the targeted player! Be creative when mentioning that the Thief\'s trap has been triggered!</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question10">What about the base Actor ?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer10">"The base Actor is called each night for them to copy one of three roles that were prepared beforehand. Once they have used all of them, the Actor can be disabled from the roles panel. The three reserve roles do not need to be added to the turn order, prefer keeping track of them without the app. "</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question11">I can do everything I want about the characters in this app!</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer11">Yes, you\'re the game master after all! You can animate your game as you wish and this app helps you to do it! The full game isn\'t handled by it, this is just a helper. A game ends only when there are no more characters in play.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question12">How can I play your special Servant through your app?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer12">This role is one of my favorites, and complex one. To play it, you need simple Villagers. Do not remove the special villagers from the turn order, and do not update the consumable powers before the servant is dead, as they can promote a simple Villager.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question13">Special notes for some roles:</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer13">The base Big Bad Wolf does not have its special turn when a Werewolf dies. The White Wolf does not have its special turn when he\'s the last Werewolf in the game. If the Wolf Hound decides to wake up at night, activate it from the roles panel. This also applies for the Wild Child when their mentor dies. Brothers and Sisters aren\'t woken up anymore when they are the last ones in play.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question14">What is the Information panel?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer14">It allows you to note down important information regarding the game, like the lovers bound by Cupid, the protected by the Protector, etc. Supplementary fields are also available to store new actions given to the eliminated players, like switching two player\'s seats, or punishing players so they turn their backs to the village during the day. This advantages the villagers and makes for a more balanced game, so be creative regarding these concepts!</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question15">What is the use of the roles panel?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer15">It allows you to manage which roles will wake up at night depending on the game\'s evolution. For example, if everyone has guessed the Witch used both of their potions, waking them up is not required anymore. The Witch can be deactivated in the roles panel. Each role that can evolve is listed in this panel. Note that not all roles wake up on the first night, but a condition can change that, like with the Wild Child.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question16">How is the player infected by the Wolf Father? What happens if they\'re the last Werewolf in play?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer16">The application does not handle the infected. If they become the last Werewolf alive, I advise to keep a Werewolf in play in the turn order to avoid forgetting about them. The infected player continues to play their original role, but also wakes up on the Werwolves turn.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question17">I can\'t complete the creation of my custom role, what is happening?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer17">You need to fill in all the data in the form, in order for the button to enable. Note also that you can\'t create an identifier key named \"NORMAL\" or \"AUTHOR\", these names are reserved by the app.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question18">Notes on the role creation page:</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer18">If you want to edit a role you previously created, enter its identifier key in the field, and the role will be overwritten with the new configuration when saving the changes.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question19">Note for language switching:</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer19">If you change the app\'s display language, roles created in another display language will not be available. Each custom role is bound to the language it has been created with. If you wish to have your new role in another language, you need to create it again from scratch. Why is it in this way? The app\'s architecture does not allow multi-language data for custom roles.</string>
    <string name="FaqView_question20">How can I reach out to the developers of this app?</string>
    <string name="FaqView_answer20">You can send me an e-mail on my address : kevin.prudhomme555@gmail.com. Be sure to use a tag like [Werewolf] in the subject so that it catches my attention!</string>

</resources>